i win the argument no no no listen if if it's about knowledge and intelligence i'm just kidding
if it's about knowledge and intelligence yes babies don't have the same knowledge and
intelligence that we do but that doesn't mean huh how do you know some babies have more knowledge
than older people yeah but they're not speaking so that's so does doesn't mean it doesn't matter
but they can do stuff well it's the same thing with the animals they're not speaking but we don't
know we know we know no they don't have how do you know because we because we have we are ahead of
the game but babies what about disabled people they say for people they don't have a disabled
disabled people could have no knowledge than other people yes disabled people or they can have less
knowledge or can have less or can have more does that justify us eating them no so then so then what
justifies eating a human versus an animal i told you already i told you already how many times i
gotta repeat myself i said i said i said that there's an animal
so
um yeah but where are you gonna put it out there let me see where are you gonna put the whole thing i
don't know i just document i know i know but so so where do guys where i am i gonna find myself in
uh possibly social media where huh social media twitter facebook something like this uh instagram
yeah instagram primarily is what i post on but oh yeah yeah where you put me in
but you can answer you can is there something you you said that you didn't want to say
what is it what is the trait that's present or missing i told you hashem wants everyone to become in a
better place so the way you say that i'm i'm gonna tell you something that you're not gonna have any
words to answer me with that okay you said if we stop killing them then everything will be all right
yes well i think that it's unnecessary to kill them okay they're living being i'm saying when you slaughter
them you slaughter them and you take them to a better place to heaven yes if hashem is gonna see
okay enough is enough we are i i'm enough i don't want to i want to stop those things he is gonna
make something that something should change
so till then he wants that yeah well you know yeshu talked about this yes you said i came to abolish
the sacrifices unless you see sacrifice but he couldn't do it he couldn't do it he did the temple's
gone no more sacrifice on the no but the temple's gone the temple's coming back through the red heifer
yeah yeah it's coming back but why is it coming back well i haven't seen it happen yet yeah but
i'm telling you it's not sacrifice it's coming back forever it's coming back very soon yeah and
what's that going to do it's what that's going to do then you're going to see oh this is what he wants
but isaiah said in the in the the age of peace of shalom that the wolf shall lay with the lamb the
lion will eat straw like the ox they shall not hurt or shakath slaughter on my holy mountain
no more i hear you but no need for a temple and that is the thing that we have it's a house of prayer
that is the thing that we have to see a house of prayer for all nations i hear you but it doesn't
it doesn't bring anything it doesn't bring a thing that it says in azaya i know i'm not saying
there's a lot of people they had a lot of knowledge and they say stuff and everything
with everyone says has something to do but i see even even what i'm saying is whatever you say
it has a meaning we create something from what we say well i'm just saying what i'm just saying i'm
just saying i'm just saying don't mention it's just saying what you you say no hosea hosea
you mention oh you mentioned you mentioned the name you mentioned the names jesus jeremiah you
do you mention oh everybody's name my dad because you want to bring them here that's all it is bring
them here yes once you mention the name he's coming oh you mentioned my name uh-huh okay what does that
mean you're saying jeremiah is here with us i'm saying that once you mention names that's why i said
i bring you abraham abraham sacrifice we sacrifice that's it yeah but abraham is stronger than all of
them abraham stronger than all of them ah well see that's maybe where you don't like it because yes
you said before abraham was i am no i i am that i am that that moses that doesn't mean nothing it
doesn't mean anything no okay so how so how do we know when there's no more murder of animals
well once the once we have the third temple then you could see what's going on
but there's going to be sacrifice of animals there so it wants if there is going to be sacrifice there
over there then it means that that's what hashem wants but so then isaiah was wrong that's correct
isaiah was wrong when he said no more he was right on that time maybe but not not in our times
so god changes his mind no every year the new year we start a new a new line a new scripture
there's a new scripture every year so but god is everlasting never changing never changing the bible
the torah never changed yeah the ten words yes that's never changed other than that we could
change everything okay and that's what i'm saying the 16 613 laws are done we don't know which is
it's from the it's from the it's from the 10 commitments so it's right it's it's it you're
lighting it up from the 10 commitments so it's still an existing thing okay well anyways
anyway joseph yes take care i believe i believe that that uh the peace on earth and shalom yeah
and the reign of hashem the reign of god on earth is when we stop slaughtering god's
creatures it needs to be over doesn't have to be right it doesn't have to be right it doesn't have
to be that you are right well it's not about me being right it's about what is right no it's about
justice no it's about your way of thinking that this is that this is not right so what proof do
you have that slaughtering a being is right i told you abraham but you said the scriptures change every
year not not about that not about that so that's the only thing that's abraham is the only unchanging
thing that's correct so abraham is god abraham was the man of god abraham is he was the man of god he
was the man of god that's correct okay the only one only one really not moses moses is is reincarnation
moses recognizes abraham or reincarnation reincarnation moses is a reincarnation of abraham
okay all right all right i will tell you a proof because moses was married to yisra
yisra wasn't jewish abraham wasn't jewish either abraham wasn't jewish yeah he's a syrian
he was a syrian he wasn't jewish he became jewish yes yeah he created the jewish and
and moses wife was the reincarnation okay makes a little sense that makes makes a little sense well
i think that there's a lot of explanations if it makes a little sense what i'm saying it makes a
little sense yeah but but but similarly melchizedek i hear you i think he's a reincarnation of the
righteous does a dog there's a deep the true righteous one but you gotta still go to the first
no sacrifice you gotta go to the first one the first one is abraham and he sacrificed that's it
so what is the ideal world what do you mean the ideal world what what would the ideal world look like
if uh if if bloodshed is okay then what is the ideal world ideal world is we should live in peace
anyways with it live in peace with bloodshed yeah yes even if it's done to you yes what do you mean
dumping you there's every i told you when you get hurt you get stronger it's it's not a bad thing
getting well i'm not just getting hurt i'm talking about being murdered but we're not we are human we
don't we don't murder anybody only only only that's below us not not above us so might makes right so
we're at the top so we can do whatever we want to those no those things yes those things that's what
hashem wants okay